

Krishna Kumar

FRONT END- DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frond End developer

2022-Present

Abservetech private limited I Madurai

- Experienced UI developer with a passion for creating user-friendly and visually appealing web interfaces using HTML,CSS,JAVASCRIPT and REACT.
- Motivated UI developer with a strong background in developing responsive , cross-browser compatible interfaces and a deep understanding of UX principles.
- Improved and expanded project platform using java-script to develop rich user interface
- Communicated with project managers and UX design to translate project requirement and business objectives into polished user interfaces.
- Collaborated with teammates to deliver valuable feature meeting business and customer needs.
- Designed UI's with frontend web frameworks, exploiting associated templates and tools to shorten development times.
- Developed application UI's via emerging front-end technologies.
- Devised site maps and mock ups for design based on proven methodologies and end-user feedback.
- Result-driven UI developer with over 1+ years of experience in creating high-quality
- web application and a proven-track record of delivering projects on time and within budget.

Service Delivery Executive (Quality control)

2019-2021

Neeyamo Enterprises | Madurai

- Attention to detail and accuracy
- Knowledge of quality control processes and procedures.
- Experience with inspection and testing of products.
- Ability to identify and resolve defects.
- Strong problem-solving skills.
- Ability to work in a team-oriented environment.
- Ability to maintain and update quality control records

CONTACTS

- 6369711784
- krishsurya1249@gmail.com
- Madurai

ABOUT ME

Experienced ui developer with over 1+ years of experience in abservetech, Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

Hardworking and passionate job seeker with strong organizational skills eager to secure entry-level ui position. Ready to help team achieve company goals.

EDUCATION

B.sc Mathematics

Thiyagarajar Acts and Science college 2016-2019

HSC

sourashtra Higher secondary school 2015-2016

SSLC

sourashtra Higher secondary school 2013-2014

SKILLS

- Typewrittering Higher(English)
- Web Developement
- HTML.CSS.JAVASCRIPT
- Boostrap,jquery
- React , FIGMA
- MY SQL
- C,C++,JAVA